export default data = [
    {
        question: "What command is used to create a new React Native project using Expo CLI?",
        options: [
            "create-react-native-app",
            "react-native init",
            "expo init",
            "npm init"],
        correct_option: "expo init"
    },
    {
        question: "Which component is used to display a list of data in React Native?",
        options: [
            "ListView",
            "FlatList",
            "ScrollView",
            "List"],
        correct_option: "FlatList"
    },
    {
        question: "How do you handle user input in React Native?",
        options: [
            "Using TextInput component",
            "Using Button component",
            "Using TouchableOpacity component",
            "Using Switch component"],
        correct_option: "Using TextInput component"
    }
    ,

    {
        question: "Which command is used to run a React Native app on an iOS simulator?",
        options: [
            "react-native run-android",
            "react-native run-ios",
            "expo start --ios",
            "expo start --android"],
        correct_option: "react-native run-ios"
    }
    ,

    {
        question: "How can you debug a React Native app?",
        options: [
            "Using console.log statements",
            "Using Reactotron",
            "Using the React Native Debugger",
            "All of the above"],
        correct_option: "All of the above"
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Which of the following lifecycle methods is not available in React Native?",
        options: [
            "componentDidMount",
            "componentWillMount",
            "componentDidUpdate",
            "componentWillUnmount"],
        correct_option: "componentWillMount"
    }
    ,

    {
        question: "What is the purpose of the AsyncStorage module in React Native?",
        options: [
            "To store data in a local SQLite database",
            "To store data in the device's file system",
            "To store data in a secure encrypted format",
            "To store data persistently on the device"],
        correct_option: "To store data persistently on the device"
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "How do you navigate between screens in a React Native app?",
        options: [
            "Using the <Navigation> component",
            "Using the <Router> component",
            "Using React Navigation library",
            "Using Redux"],
        correct_option: "Using React Navigation library"
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Which of the following is used to style components in React Native?",
        options: [
            "CSS",
            "Flexbox",
            "Inline styles",
            "Tailwind CSS"],
        correct_option: "Flexbox"
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "What is the purpose of the react-native-vector-icons library?",
        options: [
            "To add vector graphics to a React Native app",
            "To add custom fonts and icons to a React Native app",
            "To add animations to a React Native app",
            "To add navigation features to a React Native app"],
        correct_option: "To add custom fonts and icons to a React Native app"
    }

]